ampedmedia.com 2008-09-13

# Amped Media – Privacy Policy

Amped Media is dedicated to the privacy of its users. Never will the information collected by Amped Media be sold or given to another party without your prior approval. To better protect your privacy, we have established the following privacy policy that clearly defines our online technology and information collection practices. 

If you have any questions regarding the following privacy policy and its contents, please feel free to contact Amped Media using the contact information posted below.

**The policy was adopted, effective March 1, 2008.**  
This privacy policy shall constitute the entire agreement between Amped Media Inc. (“Amped Media Inc. “we” or “us”), and you governing the collection and use of your personal information at: ampedmedia.com and/or participation as an affiliate in the Amped Media affiliate program. If you are a corporation, limited liability company/corporation or any other type of business entity, the term “you” shall include any officer, executive, member, employee, consultant and/or agent of your business entity. While certain areas of our website may be accessed and viewed by the general public, you must apply and be accepted as a Member by Amped Media in order to gain complete access to the Website.  

**Information Collection and Use**  
This Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time, in our sole discretion, and such changes are effective upon their posting at ampedmedia.com. Changes may include, without limitation, changes in the types of information we collect and how we use such information. Bookmark this page and check it frequently as it is up to you to refer to this page for any amendments and/or changes to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any changes to the Privacy Policy, you must discontinue your use of the Program Website and/or terminate your Member status by contacting Amped Media Inc (support@ampedmedia.com). By visiting, accessing and/or using ampedmedia.com and/or your continued participation in the Program, you are fully subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time.   

**Information Collection**  
As part of our on-going efforts to ensure the best possible experience for all recipients of Amped Media advertising, we use cookies and web beacons to collect data from browsers to aggregate statistical information. This includes IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, domain names, access dates and times, and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of Amped Media. When you respond to an Amped Media advertisement or visit ampedmedia.com, you may be asked to provide PII (e.g. name, address, telephone number, and email address) as well as non-personally identifiable information (e.g., age or gender). The nature of the information requested will vary depending on the promotion and/or product involved. Most of this information is collected by an advertiser of a specific product or service. Amped Media does not collect, use, sell, or purchase user information that is personally identifiable.   

**Forms on Amped Media**  
Amped Media has various forms listed on our website that collect Personally Identifiable Information. The information collected from these forms are used only for the participation in the Amped Media publisher and advertiser program. None of the information collected on these forms will be sold or shared with any third party.  

**Information Use  
**  
**User Profiling  
**Amped Media stores information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their viewing preferences. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.   

**Web Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to keep track of a user’s position and settings as they move through our site. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies are required for use of the Amped Media publisher program.  

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Communications From Amped Media**

**Special Offers and Updates  
**It is policy that all new users will receive a welcome e-mail to confirm that their e-mail address and information is correct. In addition, we will send out messages in the form of e-mail to notify clients of updates to policy, and general network news. You can choose to receive these messages by using the Account Settings located within your account.  

**Customer Service Contact**  
It is important that clients understand that we require time-to-time communication to discuss issues, and other topics relating directly to a users account. We may contact clients using the Phone Number, Address, or E-mail address listed on file.   
Sharing of Personal Information  

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We do not sell any personally identifiable information to third parties.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We do not share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. However, we do store aggregate data so that we provide outside sources with general traffic statistics from our website. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site by changing their profile preferences. Every user will receive an email confirmation of their username and password as well as instructions for how to login to their account.   

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at [privacy@ampedmedia.com](mailto:privacy@ampedmedia.com).

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Email: [privacy@ampedmedia.com  
](mailto:privacy@ampedmedia.com)  
**Postal Address:**  
Amped Media Inc.  
P.O. Box 121402  
West Melbourne, FL, 32912-1402

URL: http://www.ampedmedia.com
